harri.com 2014-11-15

# policy | Harri

Privacy Policy

Harri (USA) LLC (hereinafter referred to as "Harri," "we," "us," "our," and other similar pronouns) respects the privacy of all users of www.Harri.com (including all entities, individuals, employers or their authorized agents, job candidates, and members of the general public who visit the website and/or use our services) (collectively, "users" or "you"). This Privacy Policy describes the information Harri collects through this website, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. Please review this Policy carefully and often, as it affects your legal rights and liabilities.

By using this website, you explicitly accept the collection, use, and transfer of the information provided by you in the manner described in this Policy.We will occasionally update this Policy. When we post changes to this Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies. Each time you visit this website or provide us with information, you are, by so doing, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time, without limitation or qualification.

If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use this website. If you have already registered with, or otherwise provided personal information to Harri and no longer want your information to be processed as described in the Policy, you may revoke your consent to our Privacy Policy. If you wish to do so, please email  [info@harri.com](mailto:info@harri.com) to terminate your account. However, please note that if you do terminate your account, you may not be able to use the relevant services, and your account and profile information will no longer be accessible by you or other users of our website.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Policy for information on how to contact us. We hope that the efforts we have taken to provide a secure online environment demonstrate our commitment to making your Harri experience enjoyable and worthwhile.

I. Scope

This Policy applies to our website, www.Harri.com, which is owned by Harri. It is Harri's policy to comply with data protection legislation, which regulates the processing and disclosure of information relating to individuals' personal data. As set forth more fully below in the section on Information Collection & Use, it is Harri's policy to collect and store personal information only if knowingly submitted by users through www.Harri.com, and data collected by Harri is used only to operate our business and deliver and improve upon the services we provide to our users. 

Our website contains links to other websites over which we have no control. You acknowledge that Harri bears no responsibility whatsoever for the content or data collection and usage practices of other websites to which you link from our website. We encourage you to independently review the privacy policies of those other websites so that you know how they may collect, use, and share your information. 

You acknowledge that Harri likewise has no control over and bears no responsibility for the data usage of employers or any other individuals who may access, store, or transfer your information on this site, or of third party advertising networks or other third parties with whom Harri may work to serve you personalized advertisements. We strive to provide a safe, secure environment by attempting to limit access to our database to legitimate users of our services, and we have implemented reasonable technical and strategic measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and modification of information under our control. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons or entities will never be able to defeat those measures or use your information for improper purposes. Moreover, you should be aware that any profile you create on our website may be monitored by your current employer. For all of these reasons, we encourage you not to post sensitive information or other information you would not want made public to our site.

II. Information Collection & Use

Harri collects different categories of information from its users, depending upon which of our services you use. Each user of Harri's website, by virtue of visiting www.Harri.com, is subject to the collection by Harri of certain aggregate, non-personal data such as demographic information and basic information about the user's Internet connections and site browsing patterns. Visitors are not, however, required to provide any personal information that could be used to identify them unless and until they attempt to connect with a candidate (for employers browsing the site) or view a job description and/or connect with an employer (for candidates browsing the site). In each case, it is indicated on the website whether and what personal data must be provided to use the desired functionality. It is Harri's policy to collect and store personal information only if knowingly submitted by users.

User information accessed by Harri and its agents will be used for the purpose of operating our website and delivering or improving upon the services we offer to job candidates and employers, potentially including the display of personalized content and advertising relating to users' hospitality and retail experience and preferences, either on our site or other sites with which we have a business relationship. We disclose personal information to third parties in limited circumstances, as set forth below, in the section on Information Disclosure.

We may personalize the advertising that you are shown on our website or other websites with which we have a business relationship. In order to provide this personalization, in addition to information we collect about you on our sites, we may acquire information (including both personal and aggregate data) about you from third parties who provide it to us.

o Personally Identifiable Information

  * Collection of personally identifiable information

"Personally identifiable information" is information that can be used to identify or contact you, or any other individual to whom the information may relate. Harri does not collect personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide it to us, and all personally identifiable information may be edited or deleted directly by you or at your request at any time. Depending on which of our services you use and local law, examples of personally identifiable information that we collect on our website include, but are not limited to: your name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, photograph, video clip, credit card and billing information (if you transact business with us), and information about third parties, that you provide to us if you have obtained their express and informed consent to do so.

With regard to this last category, you hereby acknowledge that when you post to our website personally identifiable information about a third party (such as, for example, names and contact information for references), by so doing, you are representing to us that you have previously obtained the third party's express and informed consent to post that particular information to our website. Similarly, you may be able to send information about our services to your personal contacts (e.g., through "Share with a Friend," "Share with a Colleague," and other sharing tools), in which case you may be required to provide us with your contact's personally identifiable information. By so doing, you confirm that you give Harri consent, on behalf of your personal contact, to receive an e-mail from Harri about the relevant service.

Harri's web site is not intended for use by children under the age of 14. In the event that we discover that personally identifiable information has been collected from a child under 14, we will delete that information from our systems.

  * Use of personally identifiable information

By registering with Harri, creating and managing your profile, or opting to provide personally identifiable information when one or more of our services permit or require the sharing of such information, you thereby consent to Harri using your personally identifiable information, subject to local law, **in the following ways:**

  * To deliver services to Harri users to facilitate the recruitment, job search, and hiring process and any other services that you request. Such services include, but are not limited to, searchable candidate and employer databases, filtering and matching functionalities, and a messaging functionality enabling registered employers and candidates to contact and communicate with one another;

  * To create and manage your account and to and publish on its site a profile for you or an employer which you represent based on information and images, including photographs and logos, that you have provided to us. If you are a candidate registered with Harri, you may elect to limit the amount of personally identifying information that is publicly available by opting for a private profile, as described in more detail below, in the section on Candidates' Privacy Option;

  * To display or share – either via postings on our website, our site's messaging functionalities, e-mail, or by postal mail – information and photographs contained within registered candidates' profiles to employers in the hospitality and retail industry, and information and images, including business logos, contained within registered employers' profiles and job postings to potential job seekers. By default, Harri will not send to employers any personally identifying information which a candidate has elected to hide from public view by opting for a private profile;

  * To develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites;

  * To provide Harri advertisements to you when you visit other websites;

  * To contact you about service-related communications, including for website and security updates, notifications of personalized content, surveys, and promotional communications about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties. You may opt out of receiving promotional communications as described below in the section on Communications from Harri;

  * To provide you with customer support;

  * To enable you to provide feedback, to contact us, and for us to respond to you;

  * To perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our website, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;

  * To enforce or exercise any rights in our Terms of Use; and

  * To perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection of your information.

We provide areas on our websites where you can publicly post information about yourself and others and communicate with others or upload content such as photographs and business logos. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may be used in our promotional materials, or may appear on our homepage, in any other section of our website, on any other websites, or when internet searches are executed on the subject of your posting.   
Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other Harri users may do with the information you publicly post or voluntarily disclose to them. Additionally, information you post in public areas of the site may be accessed, used, and stored by third parties located around the world, including those in countries that may not have comprehensive data protection legislation. For all of these reasons, we encourage you to exercise discretion with respect to the personal information you disclose.

If you apply for a position posted on our website by an employer registered with Harri, the employer may ask you to provide information on your age, gender, race, or other protected status, or for a government identity number where permitted by law. Some employers are required by law to gather this information from job applicants for reporting and record-keeping requirements. You should understand that, if provided, this information should only be used by employers in accordance with applicable law, and they should not use it in making any negative or discriminatory employment decisions. However, Harri is not responsible for the actions of such employers. Providing this information to said employer is strictly voluntary, and you will not be subject to any adverse action or treatment from Harri if you choose not to provide this information.

By providing your personal information for inclusion in Harri's database, you thereby acknowledge that you consent to your information being used as described in this Policy.

Other (Non-Personally Identifiable Information)

Collection of non-personally identifiable information

Harri also collects non-personally identifiable information, which includes aggregate and demographic information about an overall group or groups' selected population characteristics (such as postal codes, age, preferences, gender, race, ethnicity, occupation, interests, etc.), as well as basic information about users' computer hardware and software, Internet connections, and how you use our site. Harri and/or its service providers acting on Harri's behalf may use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site.

For example, we automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our site. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (See the discussion on cookies below), and any referring website address. 

Additionally, when you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to enable access to our site and to personalize your Harri experience. We may use cookies to automatically collect information about your activity on our site, such as the areas you visit, the time of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct. During your visits to other websites where we advertise, we (or third parties) may use data collected on our site to show you the type of Harri advertisements likely to be of interest to you. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can most often modify your browser setting to decline cookies. Please note, however, that if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use some of the functionalities or services offered on our site. For more information about cookies, please see the section at the end of this Policy on Internet Technologies.

We may also use standard Internet technologies such as web beacons and other similar tools to track your use of our website, and we may include web beacons in advertisements or our e-mail messages to you to learn whether messages have been received and acted upon. We do this in order to customize the services we offer to you, to deliver targeted content, and to assess the effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities. For more information on web beacons, please see the section at the end of this Policy on Internet Technologies.

Finally, we may allow third parties, including our authorized service providers or advertising companies, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may also use the tracking technologies described above, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view their advertisements so that they may deliver targeted advertisements and assess their effectiveness.

Use of non-personally identifiable information

Harri uses non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form to perform statistical analyses of its website usage (including the demographics and collective behaviors of its users), and to troubleshoot problems so that it may continually improve the usefulness and quality of the services it provides. We may provide aggregate, statistical data based on this information to our clients, current and potential business partners, advertisers, or any other third parties.

Information Disclosure

As indicated above, Harri may disclose non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site to our clients, current and potential business partners, advertisers, or any other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to our site and how those visitors use the site in order to serve advertisements to you on our site or other sites which we may have a business relationship. We may also aggregate on an anonymous basis data regarding job qualifications, age, experience level or other information relevant to the job search or competition among candidates for any such position. Such aggregated data does not identify users individually, and may be made available to employers or fellow candidates or members of the public.

Harri may also disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in limited circumstances. By registering with Harri, creating and managing your profile, or opting to provide personally identifiable information when one or more of our services permit or require the sharing of such information, you thereby consent to Harri disclosing your personally identifiable information to third parties, subject to local law, in the following ways: 

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if you create a profile, we will publish on our site the information and images that you have posted to that profile, which will be visible to any visitor of Harri's site. For more details regarding Harri's use of information you post in public areas of our site, see the section on Use of Personally Identifiable Information.

We may release personally identifiable information to companies and individuals we engage to perform functions on our behalf and to help us to operate our site and business and deliver our services to you. For example, we disclose personally identifiable information to third parties including, but not limited to, website developers, attorneys, accountants, clerical staff, website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and financial institutions (for the limited purpose of processing credit card transactions). These companies and individuals will only have access to your personal information to the extent necessary to perform services on our behalf, and only under reasonable disclosure restrictions.

We may disclose personally identifiable information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a government entity, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process, protect the rights or property of Harri, prevent a crime, or protect the personal safety of our users or the public. Specifically, but without limitation, we reserve the right to disclose such information when a visitor is in violation of our Terms of Use or other published guidelines, or engages in (or is reasonably suspected of engaging in) any harmful, infringing or illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order, and to disclose such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests, and as otherwise required by law, as well as in response to allegations of infringement. Harri also reserves the right to suspend or terminate your membership in connection with any suspected illegal or infringing activity.

We may disclose and transfer personally identifiable information to a third party who acquires any or all of Harri's assets, whether by way of acquisition, merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event Harri becomes the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Harri or its liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license, or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court. You will be notified of the sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party by e-mail or through a notice posted prominently on our website.

While Harri will use reasonable efforts to ensure that the information it discloses is subject to reasonable redisclosure restrictions, in each of the above situations, the recipients of your data may potentially be located in any country in the world, including those in countries that may not have comprehensive data protection legislation.   
By providing your personal information for inclusion in Harri's database, you thereby acknowledge that you consent to your information being disclosed to third parties as described in this Policy.

Your Choices About Your Information

As a general matter, you can choose not to provide use with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to create an account, register as a member, purchase services, connect with other registered members, or initiate other transactions on our website.

Once you decide to provide us with personally identifying information, there are a number of choices you may make regarding our use and disclosure of such information, ****as set forth below.****

Accessing, Changing, or Deleting Personal Information

Because managing one's occupation or business is a long term undertaking, we retain all of the information we gather about our users in an effort to make your repeat use of our site efficient until you change or remove your personal data as described below.

You may view and, if you wish, change the personally identifiable information you submit to us at any time by logging in to our website and going to your profile and making the necessary changes. For security reasons, we obscure your credit card number (if you have supplied one) and password and you will therefore not be able to see passwords or credit card numbers.

If you wish to delete or close your account or account profile information altogether, please email [info@harri.com](mailto:info@harri.com). An email will be sent to you to confirm that your personal information has been closed. After you close your account, you will not be able to sign in to our website or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new, separate account at any time or reactivate your previous account by following instructions we will give to you at the time you close your account. If you close your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our Terms of Use, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our website or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. We will also retain logs, demographic, and statistical information that may relate to you but do not identify your personally. Of course, if your personal information was previously accessed by others using our website, we are unable to delete the information or copies thereof from their systems. 

Before providing you with a copy of your personal information or correcting, updating, or deleting such information, we reserve the right to verify and authenticate your identity and the personal information to which you have requested access. We will respond to information access requests within the time period required by applicable law. Access, modification, or deletion of your personal information may be denied or limited by Harri if it would violate another person's rights and/or as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

If you are a registered user and have not logged in to our web site for an extended period of time, we may make your account unsearchable. If you have not logged in for a significantly long period of time, your account will expire and be scheduled for deletion. Our current expiration and deletion period for candidates is 36 months, and for employers is 24 months. We may extend or reduce these periods in order to adjust to changing hiring patterns, and upon doing so would update this notice. Deletion of expired accounts occurs on a periodic basis. You will always receive an e-mail from us before we delete your account.

Communications from Harri

Harri communicates with its users primarily through email, and for a variety of purposes.

At any time you can decline to receive promotional emails from Harri. When you register on our website, you will be given a choice as to whether you want to receive email messages from us about special offers. You may modify this consent later by visiting the Account Settings page associated with your account. You also will be given the opportunity, in any promotional email that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request.   
Note that, because Harri will occasionally need to send you certain messages in connection with your use of our site such as important service and security announcements, system status updates, account activity notifications and confirmations, and other service-related communications), you will not be able to opt out of receiving these types of communications unless you close your account with Harri altogether.

An Important Note About Candidates' Profiles

When a candidate creates a profile and posts contact information, educational background, work experience, photos, video reels, and other data to our site, that data is stored in our searchable candidate database and can be accessed by any user of our site, whether or not the user is registered with Harri. This means that any member of the general public may view the information that you post. You may control the amount of information within your profile that is accessible by setting it to private or public.

If you set your profile as public, all information contained therein is searchable and will be visible to any user of Harri's site. If you set your profile as private, all information contained therein will be used by Harri in operating its search and matching functionalities. Your full profile will also be visible to any other registered Harri user with whom you initiate a connection. However, only a limited amount of information will be publicly posted.

Specifically, when a user clicks on a profile that you have made private, the user will be able to view only your restricted profile, which includes your first name, last initial, and has a bar blocking your photo. We will hide all other information, including your contact information. If, after viewing your restricted profile, the user would like to view your full profile and initiate a connection with you, the user must request permission to do so by clicking on the connect button. Harri will then send you an email/message notifying you of the user's request. You will have the option to either deny or grant the user access to your full profile.

If you use our services to create a profile in our database of candidate profiles, you will be providing us with personally identifiable information we will use in accordance with this Policy. Your profile must not contain sensitive data relating to your (i) racial or ethnic origin, (ii) political beliefs, (iii) philosophical or religious beliefs, (iv) membership of a trade union or political party, (v) physical or mental health or genetic makeup, (vi) addictions, (vii) sexual life, (viii) the commission of criminal offences or proceedings and associated penalties or fines, or (viii) any Social Security Number or national identification number, if you set your profile as private unless you have previously sent to us your written consent that we may process your sensitive personal data, if Harri determines this to be a requirement of applicable law. If your profile does contain such data and you set your profile as public, then you agree that we may retain this information and use it in accordance with this Policy. We cannot control third parties' access to such information from our searchable database.

Cookies

Finally, Harri users may also control information collected by cookies. See the section below on Internet Technologies for more information about how Harri uses cookies, and about how to decline or delete cookies.

Security

Harri strives to protect the security and integrity of sensitive personally identifiable information provided to its site, and has implemented reasonable technical and strategic measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and modification of information under our control. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications tool, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties, such as hackers, will not be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes, during transmission of such information through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care. Users should take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure e-mail. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website at [ http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm) for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

If you create an account on our website with a password, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your login credentials (your username and password), and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of our services by you or any person or entity using your login credentials. By creating an account with Harri, you thereby agree to immediately notify Harri of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. Harri bears no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission of your information.

Contacting Harri

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with Harri, or if you are concerned that Harri has acted in violation of this Policy, please contact us online or by e-mail or postal mail as follows:

Privacy Office   
Harri (USA) LLC  
611 Broadway  
Suite 426   
New York  
NY 10012 

USA
